ILGWU 35mm Negatives of Photographs 5780 P N35
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Contact sheet 3842 (Box 111, Folder 61)
- Contact sheet 3845 (Box 111, Folder 62)
- Contact sheet 3851-2 (Box 111, Folder 63)
- Contact sheet 3852-1A (Box 111, Folder 64)
- Contact sheet 3853 (Box 111, Folder 65)
- Contact sheet 3854 (Box 111, Folder 66)
- Contact sheet 3860 (Box 111, Folder 67)
- Contact sheet 3877B (Box 111, Folder 68)
- Contact sheet 3877D (Box 111, Folder 69)
- Contact sheet 3877I (Box 111, Folder 70)
- Contact sheet 3877K (Box 111, Folder 71)
- Contact sheet 3879A (Box 111, Folder 72)
- Contact sheet 3879B (Box 111, Folder 73)
- Contact sheet 3884 (Box 111, Folder 74)
- Contact sheet 3907A (Box 111, Folder 75)
- Contact sheet 3907B (Box 111, Folder 76)
- Contact sheet 3907C (Box 111, Folder 77)
- Contact sheet 3908A (Box 111, Folder 78)
- Contact sheet 3908D (Box 111, Folder 79)
- Contact sheet 3908E (Box 111, Folder 80)
- Contact sheet 3916A (Box 111, Folder 81)
- Contact sheet 3943A (Box 111, Folder 82)
- Contact sheet 3944 (Box 111, Folder 83)
- Contact sheet 3947A (Box 111, Folder 84)
- Contact sheet 3947B (Box 111, Folder 85)
- Contact sheet 3947C (Box 111, Folder 86)
- Contact sheet 3947D (Box 111, Folder 87)
- Contact sheet 3769A (Box 111, Folder 88)
- Contact sheet 3974 (Box 111, Folder 89)
- Contact sheet 3976A (Box 111, Folder 90)
- Contact sheet 3976B (Box 111, Folder 91)
- Contact sheet 3980 (Box 111, Folder 92)
- Contact sheet 3987 (Box 111, Folder 93)
- Contact sheet 4000 (Box 111, Folder 94)
- Contact sheet 4008 (Box 111, Folder 95)
- Contact sheet 4009 (Box 111, Folder 96)
- Contact sheet 4014A (Box 111, Folder 97)
- Contact sheet 4022 (Box 111, Folder 98)
- Contact sheet 4023A (Box 111, Folder 99)
- Contact sheet 4023B (Box 111, Folder 100)
- Contact sheet 4024A (Box 111, Folder 101)
- Contact sheet 4045 (Box 111, Folder 102)
- Contact sheet 4046 (Box 111, Folder 103)
- Contact sheet 4056A (Box 111, Folder 104)
- Contact sheet 4060A (Box 111, Folder 105)
- Contact sheet 4078 (Box 111, Folder 106)
- Contact sheet 4086 (Box 111, Folder 107)
- Contact sheet 4089 (Box 111, Folder 108)
- Contact sheet 4090 (Box 111, Folder 109)
- Contact sheet 4096B (Box 111, Folder 110)
- Contact sheet 4103A (Box 111, Folder 111)
- Contact sheet 4103B (Box 111, Folder 112)
- Contact sheet 4103C (Box 111, Folder 113)
- Contact sheet 4103D (Box 111, Folder 114)
- Contact sheet 4105A (Box 111, Folder 115)
- Contact sheet 4105B (Box 111, Folder 116)
- Contact sheet 4105C (Box 111, Folder 117)
- Contact sheet 4105D (Box 111, Folder 118)
- Contact sheet 4105E (Box 111, Folder 119)
- Contact sheet 4105F (Box 111, Folder 120)
- Contact sheet 4105G (Box 111, Folder 121)
- Contact sheet 4105H (Box 111, Folder 122)
- Contact sheet 4114 (Box 111, Folder 123)
- Contact sheet 4120 (Box 111, Folder 124)
- Contact sheet 4123 (Box 111, Folder 125)
- Contact sheet 4124A (Box 111, Folder 126)
- Contact sheet 4130 (Box 111, Folder 127)
- Contact sheet 4144A (Box 111, Folder 128)
- Contact sheet 4144B (Box 111, Folder 129)
- Contact sheet 4144C (Box 111, Folder 130)
- Contact sheet 4148A (Box 111, Folder 131)
- Contact sheet 4148B (Box 111, Folder 132)
- Contact sheet 4158A (Box 111, Folder 133)
- Contact sheet 4158 (Box 111, Folder 134)
- Contact sheet 4158C (Box 111, Folder 135)
- Contact sheet 4158D (Box 111, Folder 136)
- Contact sheet 4158E (Box 111, Folder 137)
- Contact sheet 4158F (Box 111, Folder 138)
- Contact sheet 4158G (Box 111, Folder 139)
- Contact sheet 4158H (Box 111, Folder 140)
- Contact sheet 4158I (Box 111, Folder 141)
- Contact sheet 4200 (Box 111, Folder 142)
- Contact sheet 4206 (Box 111, Folder 143)
- Contact sheet 4222 (Box 111, Folder 144)
- Contact sheet 4223 (Box 111, Folder 145)
- Contact sheet 4227 (Box 111, Folder 146)
- Contact sheet 4230 (Box 111, Folder 147)
- Contact sheet 4235 (Box 111, Folder 148)
- Contact sheet 4236 (Box 111, Folder 149)
- Contact sheet 4243 (Box 111, Folder 150)
- Images digitized from the collection. (Box 112)